educake.co.uk 2016-06-25

# Educake - Online Formative Assessment for Science Homework and Classwork

We will treat any information you give us with great care.

We will not give your details to other companies.

Everything is kept on a safe and secure server.

**Click here if you want more detail...**

**Educake Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how Educake uses and protects any information that you give Educake when you use this website.

Educake is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, such as your name and email address, it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

By registering with Educake and using our services, you give your consent to the use of your personal data as set out in this Privacy Policy.

Educake may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st April 2012. 

**What we collect**

We may collect the following information: 

  *     * your name
  * your school name
  * contact information including email address
  * other information relevant to market research

**What we do with the information we gather**

We need this information to enable you to use our products and services. We also use it to:

  * Understand how our products and services are used,
  * Improve our products and services,
  * Keep internal records,
  * Occasionally send emails about new products or updates to the products,
  * Contact you by email, phone or mail for market research. 

**Student data**

We keep records of students’ scores when using Educake, which are available to teachers of that school only. For example, a teacher might want to analyse the performance of students on a certain topic. Students do not have access to any information of other students.  
The Educake website does not provide students with any means to communicate directly with each other. For example, there are no chat rooms.

**Security**

Information is stored on a secure server. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a common small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. We usually do not have any control over the content of these websites. Because of this, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting these sites, so these sites are not governed by this privacy statement. Instead, they will be governed by the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * if you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at support@educake.co.uk

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email support@educake.co.uk.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

We do not store any customers' credit card information.
